Here you are.
Th-Thank you.
Two spoons...
Woo!
You want us to eat together?!
You've really set me up, Hinako-san!
It's so cute.
Relax...
She's going to get all up in my face
again if she finds out I'm flustered.
She gave us two spoons.
You may as well have some.
Really? Can I? Yay!
Thank y—
This situation is kind of...
What's wrong? You aren't eating.
It feels like we're dating, doesn't it?
Did that get your heart racing?
C-Could you not make stuff up?!
I do this with Nacchan all the time!
In fact, I wouldn't even
mind sharing one spoon.
Here you go.
She's fighting back!
She got me just the right
amount of strawberry sauce, too.
Also, her face is so red!
Why is she still insisting
she isn't blushing?!
This isn't fair!
Just throw it in already!
Hang on...
Are you frozen?
Did that startle you?
What are you going on about? So stupid.
He nommed it! He nommed it!
AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                 AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!                                                   AHHH, I FED HIM!
You're stupid for calling me stupid!
Besides...
You're the one who gets
excited over stuff like this.
I-I-Indirect kiss!
Well?
I-If I pull back now, I'll have lost.
Until Yukiya really sees me as a girl,
I absolutely can't lose.
You have a goofy look on your face.
Lame! You're so annoying!
I Want to End This Love Game
Episode 5
My Childhood Friend Comes In the Morning
Time to eat.
Yum!
Mom,
Night shift must've been tough!!
I made your favorite cheese katsu
today!!
They came out nice.
Good luck at work!
Miku
m 26.829 16.371 l -225.831 355.029 282.84 573.699 320.169 555.03 341.499 525.699 346.839 379.029 429.501 325.701 458.841 224.37 96.171 37.701
Thanks for breakfast.
I'm going to use this
to finally stun Yukiya.
Great.
Mom, can we get another slice of bread?
The egg's ruined.
It looked better than last time...
Was it too hot?
That must be Miku-chan.
Isn't it a bit early?
Morning.
Sorry I came early.
She has her hair down.
Wh-What's up?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, actually, I wanted to
ask you for a favor.
I hurt my finger during
gym class yesterday,
so I can't tie my hair properly.
So...
Could you tie my hair?
O-Okay.
Come in.
Thanks.
Is your finger okay, though?
It's a trap!
She's taking advantage
of the fact that it's morning
and I'm not emotionally ready!
'Kay.
Tie it up neatly, please.
She's too pretty! I can't
look directly at her!
O-Okay.
I'm just tying her hair. No big deal.
Think about how many times
I've done Wakana's hair.
I'm so fast at making braids,
I could write it in my resume.
You aren't going to get my heart pounding
just by touching your hair.
Crap... Her hair...
It smells so good.
Did you use something?
Yup, I did.
Dad sent me some new stuff.
Hm? Uh-oh, what's wrong?
Your hands aren't moving.
Did your heart skip a beat?
Your hair got in my nose.
I was about to sneeze.
I could do anything to her
with her back turned to me.
She's being cocky.
You know...
You're lying about stubbing your finger.
I-It's not a lie.
You can't even tie your hair.
How could you bandage
your hand so neatly?
Such an elaborate trick
first thing in the morning.
You really are needy, aren't you?
You used to like having your head patted
like Wakana did, remember?
But I guess now it means something
different to you, doesn't it?
There. You lose.
He kissed me!
He actually kissed me!
He finally went and did it!
Sensei! He kissed me!
What? What?! Ew!
Why did you think that would be okay?!
Shoujo manga techniques fail again.
Speaking of when we were kids...
I liked touching your ears, remember?
They're
so squishy!
Stop
it!
Your ears are still soft.
Hey!
What's this? Your ears are getting warm.
Is your heart pounding?
Y-You're imagining it.
Your ears are softer.
Go touch your own.
Then...
Why don't we compare?
Thanks!
squish      squish      squish      squish      squish      squish      squish      squish      squish
Gotta have my morning ear massage.
R-R-Right?
Ear massages regulate your
autonomous nervous system
and even help you lose weight, right.
What are you, axolotls?
You should probably do it too, Wakana.
Pass.
More importantly, it's almost 8.
Already?!
I-I'm going to get my bag.
Want me to get your shoes for you?
It's fine.
Stop meddling to try to hide
your shame. It's annoying.
Not that it's surprising,
but his hand's grown bigger.
Maybe I'll ask him
to put my hair up again.
We're off.
Her high school uniform's nice, but
her middle school one was cute, too
Wakana, there are more
acupressure points on the ears
than on the neck.
Okay, okay, onii.
Oh yeah, what did you do with
your middle school uniform?
I think I'll give it to my
mom's friend's daughter.
She's starting next year.
What's wrong? You look disappointed.
Do you want me to wear it?
And then what, perv?
You're so cold.
Don't you have any good memories
attached to your uniform?
I guess I can keep it
if you really insist.
O-Oh? I see. Huh.
"Cold" my butt!
He definitely looked like
he wanted me to wear it!
He can be a real perv sometimes.
What if I made a move
on him wearing this?
No, no, that would make me the pervert!
I Want to End This Love Game
So, Wakana,
why didn't you tell them you
have a curfew and come home?
My friend wanted my advice on something.
I lost track of the time
and forgot to message you.
That'd better be true.
Out so late? All dressed up?
Where were you talking to them?
Who's your friend?
Is your friend a guy or a girl?
Come on!
Shut up!
Mom just gave me
the same lecture a minute ago!
For a whole hour!
I know I should have messaged Mom,
but you don't need get
on my case too, Onii!
I'm just worried about you.
You're such a pain!
Why do I need to tell you
about everything?!
You think I'm the kind of person who does
bad things behind your back, don't you?
That's not really the point.
Forget it.
Go away!
Fine, fine.
I messed up.
Miku
Yukiya?
I'm done with my chores.
Ready for some Squidtoon?
What's wrong?
You sound a bit bummed.
No, well, Wakana and I just...
Actually, wanna go to
the convenience store for a bit?
Okay, sure.
I was just in the mood
for something sweet.
Sad. Wakana-chan hates you.
So now you're all bummed.
You can be a bit excessive
about Wakana-chan.
Curfew's important, but she gets
annoyed by you because you keep prying.
Maybe you should trust her some more.
Again, it isn't about
whether I trust her or not.
It's just not safe coming home so late.
Especially because she's cute.
I get it, but...
Aren't you happier if she comes
home smiling after having fun
than if she has to come home because her
annoying brother's getting on her case?
Read
Today
Just
read
Let's just forget about it.
What were you doing out so late?
I was at the culture festival after-party.
Smiling, huh?
Why not help her out when
she really needs the help?
Don't be dumb.
I can't swoop in at the last
minute like in a drama.
That's why I'm being this way.
She gets annoyed when I worry
about her preemptively.
But I have to help her
when she's in a pinch?
That's stupid.
But wouldn't it be pretty badass
if you were the hero who
showed up when she's in a pinch?
This kid...
You'd better be careful, too.
You have a cute face, if nothing else.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Also, I'm totally fine.
No worries.
I have a pretty painful punch.
And I can run away if I have to.
I'm a fast runner.
At night,
push the button
Seriously, what's with the sighing?
No, that's messed up for real.
Right? It's hella messed.
Messed up for real for real.
Straight up messed up.
So messed up that it's messed up.
Told you.
If you're that worried about me,
I'd love if you protected me, Yukiya.
You don't even care about
what I'm going through.
Huh?
I kinda get how Wakana-chan feels.
The first time you use a knife,
the first time you go out with friends...
Girls get lectured
all sorts of ways every time.
It makes you go, "Urgh..."
The same happened to me, too.
It's frustrating the moment it happens.
But it's because I'm cared for.
And of course she appreciates that.
I'm sure Wakana-chan understands
that you're worried for her.
You've always been her big brother.
Holding her hand so she doesn't fall.
Sticking by her side when she's crying.
Patting her head when she's sad.
Letting her hang out when
she can't keep up with her friends.
I've done all that for her?
I might have embellished a bit.
Anyway, point is, she gets
why people are worried.
Maybe she didn't want to
be scolded by her brother.
She probably wanted you
to be on her side.
You don't need get on my case too, Onii!
Dunno about that.
Pakico    Café au lait
Creamy Frozen Smoothie
A flavor that melts on your tongue
Coffee & Milk
Halfsies.
He can go a bit overboard,
but the way he's always
a proper brother...
There's a new version
of the one we always buy.
That's what I like about him.
Ice Pearls
Mitarashi Dango
Flavor
Secret Sauce
Recipe
Limited Time
Thanks.
I know I said too much,
but I have a feeling I'll do
the same thing if she does it again.
And she'll get angry again.
And then...
You're so lecturey.
Trashy
I like my trashy guy more. He gets me.
Peace! Woo! 'Sup dawg, you seein' this?
I don't need you anymore, Onii.
Bye-bye!
I might lose Wakana.
You're an idiot.
Don't worry. Just trust her.
You always brush it off like it's nothing.
It's not a matter of trust.
No girl's going to stick around
with her older brother forever.
Especially with the way I am.
She might just wander off with
some cute guy who sounds fun.
You're a perfectly awesome big brother.
You'll be fine.
You blushed!
Ice Pearls
Mitarashi Dango
Flavor
Limited Time
Stop messing with me!
Will you always be by my side, too?
What was that?
Nothing.
Wakana, I bought popsicles.
H-Hey...
I took it too far earlier.
It isn't that I don't trust you.
I should have let it go.
Well...
It was my fault for worrying you, too.
Also...
Here.
I was borrowing these.
Koi-Kyun
Can I borrow the rest later?
Okay.
Thanks for the popsicle.
Koi-Kyun
Come on!
You left your sticky-notes in!
I told you to stop it!
S-Sorry, Wakana!
I'll take them off now!
Onii, you idiot!
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Wants to Sleep Over
I finally got all the sticky-notes
off, but the worst part
is that I can kind of guess what Onii
was thinking when he put them there,
and it's so gross!
"Be mine."
Ew! Ew! Ew!
Next episode: "My Childhood Friend
Wants to Sleep Over."
Don't miss it.